My name is Suresh Visaria. I am
associated with Aditya Birla Sunlife Insurance Company. According to
me,
dedication, follow-up and discipline are
important for an advisor in his business. Every advisor
should have them and what he should not have is that an advisor should
not cheat the customer, do not
hide anything and do not
call anything false. In our life insurance business, there
should be dedication. How to be successful is to
meet the customer regularly and give him a
satisfying service. The most important thing is that
we have to serve the customer. If the customer
gets the service, he will remain with us.
Apart from this, they should have a trust in themselves. They should
not mislead anyone, that builds the customer.
Today, I am
also involved in social activities. I have accumulated goodwill among the people, so
that trust has been built for me. If you
ask anyone in your area, there is
goodwill there in my name. So, according to that, I do
not face much difficulty in doing business right now
and I protect people in life.
[Music]